Inventory of the Paul N. McCloskey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 279)
  - Printed matter
    - Committee prints and Executive branch printed matter relating to budget, taxes, economy, 1981-1982
    - Land use, land planning, parkways, DDT, energy, environment, population, urban issues, 1968-1982 (Box 459)
  - Miscellany, 1982 (Box 460)
    - National youth service
    - Defense budget
    - Gallant Eagle II
    - Nuclear weapons
    - Military airlift--Lockheed C-5B vs. Boeing 747
    - California Conservation Corps
    - Military construction
    - Pacific Eagle casework
    - Pratt & Whitney's letters
    - Military academy appointees since 1967
    - Atlantic Council
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 461)
    - McCloskey weekly column, 1973
    - Constituent day procedures, 1974-1976
    - New Hampshire McCloskey schedule and follow-up letters, 1971 fall
    - McCloskey clippings, 1971
    - North Carolina briefing book press copy, 1971 August 24
  - Miscellany (Box 462)
    - Transcriptions of Laos tapes
    - Office of Federal Contract Compliance programs, 1974-1980
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 463)
    - "7252--Invitation--Washington accept" to "7262--Invitation--Out of town regret,", 1979-1981
    - "7252--Invitation--Washington accept" to "7262--Invitation--Out of town regret, 1979-1981 (Box 464)
    - "7006--Personal--Memberships and endorsements" to "7252--Invitation--Washington accept,", 1980-1982 (Box 465)
    - "7260--Invitation--Out of town accept" to "7262--Invitation--Out of town regret,", 1981-1982 (Box 466)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "N--Names,", 1975-1976
    - "M--Members of Congress,", 1975-1976
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 467)
    - "14010--Civil rights--Abortion--Pro" to "14110--Civil rights--Gay rights,", 1982
  - Miscellany
    - Republican Party platform
    - Charlie Wilson speech, 1980 May 29
    - West Bank "Dear Colleague" letter
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 468)
    - "8600--Department file/Casework--Academies general" to "9040--Department file/Casework--Housing and Urban Development,", 1981-1982
    - "9043--Department file/Casework--Housing and Urban Development--Community development" to "9375--Department file/Casework--Special Trade Representative,", 1982 (Box 469)
    - "10000--Aging" to "10546--Agriculture--Water reclamation,", 1982
  - Miscellany
    - Saga case
    - San Joaquin windfall profits tax case
    - Case for McCloskey timber sales
    - Pauley oil case
    - Optimum space systems
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 470)
    - "10549--Agriculture--California water issues" to "13032--Business--Chrysler--Copies,", 1982
    - "13070--Business--Patent reform bill" to "16060--Congress--1982 congressional tax deduction," (Box 471)
    - "16070--Congress--Pensions" to "21040--Environment--Clean Air Act--General statement,", 1981-1982 (Box 472)
    - "17095--Crime and justice--Legal Services Corporation" to "19560--Education--Vocational,", 1981-1982 (Box 473)
    - "20000--Energy" to "20175--Energy--Synthetic fuels,", 1981-1982 (Box 474)
  - Printed matter
    - Nuclear weapons
    - Public letter from McCloskey to Governor Edmund Brown concerning balanced budget amendment, 1982
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 475)
    - "20180--Energy--U.S. Department of Energy" to "21230--Environment--Sagebrush rebellion,", 1981-1982
    - "22000--Federal government" to "25685--Labor-- Worker's compensation,", 1981-1982 (Box 476)
    - "22500--Health--Mission Health Center" to "23540--Housing--Rent control,", 1982 (Box 477)
    - "23550--Immigration" to "24560--International relations--Détente--Con,", 1981-1982 (Box 478)
    - "24565--International relations--El Salvador aid" to "24800--International relations--World peace--General statement,", 1981-1982 (Box 479)
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file, 1979-1980
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file, 1979-1980 (Box 480)
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file, 1979-1980 (Box 481)
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor/Cosign correspondence file, 1979-1980.
    Arranged by general subject terms
  - Miscellany. Social Security speech, 1982 May 18
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "26500--Merchant Marine and fisheries" to "27217--Population information--Catholic leaders,", 1982
    - "27300--Population information--Title X: Family planning" to "28500--Social Security,", 1982 (Box 482)
    - "28510--Social Security--reform" to "29600--Taxes--Single vs. married taxpayers,", 1981-1982 (Box 483)
    - "29610--Taxes--Tax bill" to "30590--Trade--Trade with communist countries--Pro,", 1982 (Box 484)
  - Miscellany
    - National Association of Manufacturers' International Trade Policy Committee, San Francisco, 1982
    - Guadalupe corridor--San Jose transit mall
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 485)
    - "31000--Transportation--General" to "32000--Inactive files,", 1981-1982
  - Miscellany
    - Guadalupe corridor--San Jose transit mall
    - Sweeney Ridge, 1981-1982 (Box 486)
    - McCloskey speeches, press releases, clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 487)
    - Material on miscellaneous legislation
    - Copies of important papers, statements, testimony, etc., containing McCloskey clippings, statements, Congressional Record reprints, etc., 1969-1980
  - Subject files (numeric file codes) (Box 488)
    - "1010--Calendar letters,", 1980-1981
    - "2700--Complimentary letters" to "3900--Photo files,", 1980-1981
  - Miscellany (Box 489)
    - Clippings, 1981-1982
    - Campaign miscellaneous, 1982.
      Chiefly correspondence
    - Clippings, 1981-1982 (Box 490)
  - Staff members' files--Donna (Environmental), 1976-1978 (Box 491)
    - Boundary Waters Canoe Area
    - Water--Drought
    - Clean air
    - Ban the can
    - Federal Fungicide, Insecticide, and Rodenticide act
    - Airline deregulation
    - Earthquakes
    - Recombinant DNA
    - Locks, dams, dam safety
    - Solid wastes
    - Redwoods
    - Transportation and highways
    - Wilderness
    - Coastal zone management
    - Noise pollution
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file. Tuna/Porpoise (marine mammals) files, 1976-1977 (Box 492)
  - Miscellany (Box 493)
    - Press releases and clippings, 1980-1982
    - Names and addresses, by California county
    - Press books with names and addresses, 1978-1982 (Box 494)
    - Raiders bill
    - Senate campaign
    - Budget
    - General legislation, 1982
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "3000--Press"
    - "7000--General correspondence"
    - "13000--Business"
    - "13080--Business--Small Business Innovation Act"
    - "15000--Communications--AT&T"
    - "18500--Economy and budget--Constitutional amendment"
    - "23500--Housing--Housing/Banking legislation"
    - "29500--Taxes--Tax issues general"
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1978-1982 (Box 495)
    - Study of ocean rate disparities, 1978
    - Floor notebook
    - To improve the international ocean commerce transportation system of the U.S., H.R. 4374, 1981-1982
    - Natural gas VTS pipeline safety, 1979-1980
    - To strengthen the shipbuilding mobilization base and protect strategic supply sources, H.R. 5020, 1982
    - Longshoremen and Harbor Workers Compensation Act, H.R. 25, 1982
  - Printed matter
    - Maritime Administration
    - Fishery conservation
    - Ports and waterways safety
    - Fiscal year 1983 budget
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file (Box 496)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1981
    - Endangered species (Box 497)
    - Federal Maritime Commission
    - Fisheries (coastal, freshwater, pelagic tuna)
    - 200-mile zone
    - GIFA (Governing international fishery agreements)
    - Boundary disputes
    - Maritime Administration authorization
    - Correspondence (Box 498)
    - Speeches, newsletters, and press statements
    - Law of the Sea speeches, testimony, key documents, addresses, general correspondence, 1976-1982 (Box 499)
  - Miscellany. Coastal barrier resources bill--Maps and briefing book, 1982
  - Printed matter. American Indian, 1977
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1981-1982 (Box 500)
    - Maritime torts
    - Marine mammals
    - Merchant marine
    - Port bills
    - User fees
    - International Longshoremen's Association
    - 50-mile rule
    - Public Health Service hospitals
    - Veteran's status bill
    - Gambling on U.S.-flag vessels
    - Unions and union officials
    - Omnibus bill (96th Congress) (Box 501)
    - Environmental and Energy Study Conference weekly bulletins, 1982
    - Tuna war, 1982
    - Maritime Administration and budget fiscal year, 1983
    - Maritime Administration fiscal year, 1982
- Washington, D.C. office (Box 502)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file
    - A bill to improve the international ocean commerce transportation system of the U.S., also known as the Shipping Act of 1982, H.R. 4374
    - Operating differential subsidy (Box 503)
    - Longshoremen's compensation, H.R. 25
    - Strategic shipbuilding, H.R. 5020
    - Safe containers, H.R. 6732
    - Maritime satellite communication
    - Oil rigs
    - WAMPA
    - Title XI
    - Maritime subsidies
    - Health and humanitarian vessels (surplus vessels), H.R. 4828
    - Ocean constitution, H.R. 3782
    - IRS (Internal Revenue Service)/Cruise ships, H.R. 3191
    - American Bureau of Shipping
    - Foreign liability for stevedoring services, H.R. 6829
    - Puerto Rico passenger service, H.R. 1489
    - Exception to the Jones Act/Forest products
    - Hearings and reports (97th Congress), 1981-1982 (Box 504)
    - Law of the Sea, 1981-1982 (Box 505)
    - Alaska oil (Box 506)
    - Canadian diversion
    - Jamaican bauxite sale
    - Sale of surplus butter to New Zealand
    - Israel--Wheat
    - Cargo preference
    - Title IV
    - Coal ports
    - Coast Guard
    - Coastal zone management
    - Outer continental shelf
    - Conservation
    - Barrier island
    - Wetlands--Matagorda Island (Texas)
    - Closure of San Francisco Customs Office
    - Merchant marine readiness/defense
    - Military sealift command
    - American controlled shipping
    - Build and charter
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 507)
    - "7150--Employment inquiry--A" to "7504--Thank you (received or sent),", 1980-1982
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 508)
    - "7005--Family personal" to "7450--General requests--L,", 1980-1982
  - Miscellany
    - Follow-up name list for McCloskey, 1981 December 8
    - Information files 1 - 17.
      Contains McCloskey speeches, testimony, press releases, letters, etc., prepared for public distribution
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 509)
    - "7150--Employment inquiry--S" to "8500--Washington visitor--Z"
  - Miscellany
    - McCloskey personal friends--Counties
    - Californians for McCloskey roster
    - Computer correspondence, 1982
  - Campaign/Political file--Senate campaign. Chiefly clippings (Box 510)
    - Pete Wilson debate
    - John Schmitz
    - 1982 senate candidates
    - Senate race--Polls, issues, etc.
  - Miscellany
    - Foreign language studies group in Congress
    - Vietnam veterans in Congress, 1981
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor correspondence, 1981-1982
  - Campaign/Political file--Senate campaign, 1981 (Box 511)
    - Clippings, correspondence, schedules, memoranda, press releases
    - Bob Dornan
    - Edmund Brown
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 512)
    - "13070--Business--Patent rights"
    - "13077--Business--Vinson Trammell Act and Renegotiation Board,", 1977-1980
    - "22035--Federal government--Cost accounting standards,", 1981-1982
    - "22035--Federal government--Office of Federal Contract Compliance Programs,", 1981-1982
  - Printed matter. Bicentennial Times commemorative reprints
  - Sponsor/Cosponsor bill file, 1981 (Box 513)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "17060--Crime and justice--McCloskey handgun control bill" to "17090--Crime and justice-- 60 Minutes-- Con,", 1981-1982
    - "26500--Merchant marine and fisheries,", 1979-1981 (Box 514)
  - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee file, 1981-1982 (Box 515)
    - Shippers councils
    - Tariffs
    - Forest products
    - Regulatory reform
    - Maritime Administration promotional features
    - Maritime labor
    - Fiscal year 1983 Maritime Administration authorization
    - Maritime torts
    - Buy off subsidy
    - Shipping Act of 1982, H.R. 4374. Testimony and papers (Box 516)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 517)
    - "18500--Economy and budget" to "18550--Economy and budget--Constitutional amendment,", 1981-1982
    - "13075--Business--Renegotiation,", 1977-1979 (Box 518)
    - "2500--Political and district liaison" to "2700--Outstanding complimentary letters and statements,", 1977-1978 (Box 519)
  - Miscellany
    - Bill Cohen
    - Republican Research Committee
    - 1978 position papers
    - General Chesarek
  - Subject file (numeric file codes) (Box 520)
    - "24740--International relations--South Africa" to "29525--Taxes--Capital gains,", 1981-1982
  - Miscellany
    - Set-aside
    - "Dear Colleagues"
    - Small Business Innovation Act
- California district office (Box 521)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "J-Environment" to K--San Mateo County--Pacifica beach erosion,", 1971
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject term) (Box 522)
    - "Labor, Dept. of--BACOP" to "Publications distributed,", 1970
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 523)
    - "E-Economy--General" to "I-Congress--Eighteen year old vote,", 1971
    - "Q--Academies,", 1972-1973 (Box 524)
    - "X--Casework--Acknowledgements--No action" to "X--Casework--Selective service N-Z,", 1972-1973
  - Miscellany. Millbrae mudslides
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject) (Box 525)
    - "Conservation--General" to "El Granada (beach erosion),", 1970
  - Miscellany (Box 526)
    - Letters sent, 1972
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, 1974
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject) (Box 527)
    - "ABAG (Association of Bay Area Governments)" to "Conservation--Environmental teach-in,", 1970
  - Miscellany, 1975 (Box 528)
    - Stockton sewage
    - Energy, natural gas
    - Bill Corson
    - Merchant Marine and Fisheries Committee
    - Maritime oversight hearings
    - Maritime seapower/war risk insurance
    - Environmental Protection Agency
    - Pesticides
    - Wednesday Group
    - Vietnam
    - Privacy
    - Gun control
    - Stanford Medical Center
    - Passive restraints
    - Audit of construction grants
    - Law of the sea
    - Maritime subsidy program
    - Nuclear waste
    - Jobs creation
    - Petroleum storage
    - Tanzania kidnapping of Stanford students
  - Casework. "Civil service" to "Servicemen M-Z,", 1974 (Box 529)
  - Miscellany, 1975 (Box 530)
    - Energy, natural gas, coal, oil shale, geothermal
    - Outer continental shelf
    - Citizens Action Committee, Inc.
    - Dingell bill
    - Customs penalty law change
    - Migrant laborer case
    - USS Savannah
    - Louisiana
    - Hebert rule--Georgine Laub (Stanford)
    - Knecht
    - KGO Radio
    - Albie Wells
    - Privacy
    - Alex Jane Noble
    - Youth
    - Nuclear power
  - Casework, 1974-1975 (Box 531)
    - "Veterans A-H" to Wages--Pay board"
    - Academies
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1973-1975 (Box 532)
  - Campaign/Political file (Box 533)
    - "County clerk documents" to "San Mateo Post,", 1968
  - Casework. "Academies" to "Welfare,", 1969 (Box 534)
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject term) (Box 535)
    - "Calls for Peter" to "Expenses and paid bills--District,", 1969
    - "Recommendations--General" to "State, Department of,", 1969 (Box 536)
    - "Libraries--General" to "Recommendations,", 1969 (Box 537)
    - "Contracts" to "Leslie Salt,", 1969 (Box 538)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 539)
    - "A--Appropriations--General" to "D--Volunteer army,", 1971
  - Miscellany. Addresses
  - Casework. "Servicemen and veterans" to "Welfare" and "Miscellaneous,", 1971 (Box 540)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 541)
    - "Z--Political--General,", 1969-1971
  - Campaign/Political file. Correspondence, 1967 (Box 542)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 543)
    - "A--Education--Higher" to "F--Foreign affairs--Vice president,", 1973
    - "G--Government--Budget" to "I--Transportation--Rapid transit,", 1973 (Box 544)
    - "K--San Mateo County--Probe" to "R--Office--Interns,", 1970-1971 (Box 545)
  - Casework. Veterans and miscellaneous, 1972-1973 (Box 546)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1972
  - Miscellany (Box 547)
    - Clippings, 1970
    - Card file containing names, addresses of contributors, A - Mc, and dates of contributions, 1971-1972 (Box 548)
    - Card file containing names, addresses of contributors, M -Z, and dates of contributions, 1971-1972 (Box 549)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 550)
    - "A--Grants--General" "C--California--San Francisco Bay Area,", 1970-1972
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject term) (Box 551)
    - "Employment (unemployment)" to "Letters from Pete,", 1970
  - Miscellany. 1970 campaign
  - Casework (Box 552)
    - "Academies, general" to "Selective Service--Z,", 1971-1972
    - "Servicemen A-G" to "Welfare/Food stamps,", 1972 (Box 553)
    - "Servicemen M-P to "Veterans aid A-B,", 1973 (Box 554)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 555)
    - "R--Office--Equipment" to "S--Invitations--Regrets and past date April 1972--Accepted,"
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject term) (Box 556)
    - "Publications--Requested" to "Youth for service--'Streetworker' program,", 1970
  - Casework. "Agriculture, Department of" to "Labor,", 1973 (Box 557)
  - Miscellany (Box 558)
    - Press releases and clippings, 1972
    - Press releases and clippings, 1971 (Box 559)
  - Casework (Box 560)
    - "Academies" to "Social Security,", 1968-1969
    - "Miscellaneous,", 1968-1969
    - "Postal Service, A-M" to "Veterans, H- P,", 1975 (Box 561)
    - "Civil service" to "Miscellaneous, A-L,", 1975 (Box 562)
    - "Social Security, A-G" to "Servicemen, A-G,", 1975 (Box 563)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1975 (Box 564)
  - Miscellany
    - 1974 primary and general election--Thank yous, correspondence
    - Memoranda from McCloskey, 1974
    - Memoranda from district office staff, Washington, D.C. staff, and EFS (Elizabeth Stevenson, field representative), 1974-1975
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "O--Office--Employment,", 1975
    - "A--District--Economic and Social Opportunities Inc." to "O--Office--Employment,", 1973-1975 (Box 565)
    - "O--Office--1974 paid bills and bank statements" to "V--News media--Press--General," (Box 566)
  - Subject file (no file codes, alphabetical by subject term) (Box 567)
    - "ABAG (Association of Bay Area Governments" to "Indian material--South Hillsborough School,", 1968-1969
  - Printed matter. Reprints of Congressional Record and letters from Pete, which appear to have been a newspaper column, 1968 (Box 568)
  - Legislative file. "Agriculture" to "Ways and Means--Tax increase,", 1969 (Box 569)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes) (Box 570)
    - "U--Political--Group lists" to "V--News media--McCloskey press January 1973,"
  - Casework. Miscellaneous, referral, servicemen, veterans, 1974-1975 (Box 571)
  - Campaign/Political file. Correspondence and miscellaneous material concerning the campaign, 1967 (Box 572)
  - Casework (Box 573)
    - Immigration, Internal Revenue Service, Labor, NAS Moffett Field, NASA Ames, Postal Service, prisons, referrals, 1976
    - Servicemen, Small Business Administration, Social Security, Veterans education/home loan, 1977 (Box 574)
    - Civil Service, CHAMPUS, Customs, Housing, Department of State, Immigration, 1977 (Box 575)
  - Letters sent (pink copies), 1977
  - Casework. Veterans, 1976-1977 (Box 576)
  - Office file--Memoranda from EFS (Elizabeth Stevenson, field representative), Washington staff, district office staff, and McCloskey, 1976
  - Miscellany
    - District office checkbook
    - 1976 paid bills
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "P--Political--Constituent meetings" to "R--Requests--Referrals,", 1977
  - Letters sent (pink copies), 1977
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "A3--District (Cities)--Coastside--Pescadero water supply" to "A3--District (Cities)--Woodside,", 1974-1978 (Box 577)
    - "A1--District (Santa Clara County)--Assemblyman Vic Calvo" to "A2--District (San Mateo County)--Stanford Research Institute,", 1975-1977 (Box 578)
    - "A--District--Education--Higher" to "C2--California--Metropolitan Transportation Commission" (Box 579)
    - "J--Environment--Corps of Engineers jurisdiction (Breaux-Wright amendment) Wetlands issue,"
    - "Civil rights,", 1975-1976
  - Casework (Box 580)
    - Immigration Q-Z, Internal Revenue Service, Labor--Workers compensation, Miscellaneous, Postal Service, Prison, Referrals, Servicemen A-G, 1976-1977
    - Social Security, Servicemen, CHAMPUS, Civil service, Veterans Administration, 1975-1976 (Box 581)
    - CHAMPUS, Civil service, Consumer affairs, Department of State, Employment problems, Grants and loans, Housing, Immigration, 1978 (Box 582)
    - Internal Revenue Service, Miscellaneous, Labor--Workers compensation and black lung, Postal Service, Prisons, Referrals, Servicemen A-G, 1978 (Box 583)
    - Servicemen H-Z, Small Business Administration, Social Security, Student grants/loans, Veterans Administration--Education/Home, 1978 (Box 584)
    - Veterans Administration, 1978 (Box 585)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1978-1979
  - Casework (Box 586)
    - The arts, CHAMPUS, Child support enforcement, Consumer affairs, Department of State, Department of the Treasury, Employment problems, Federal Communications Commission, Housing, Immigration, Internal Revenue Service, 1978-1979
    - Labor--Workers compensation and black lung, Miscellaneous, Office of Personnel Management, Postal Service, Prisons/Crime, Referrals, Servicemen A-G, 1978-1979 (Box 587)
    - Servicemen H-Z, Social Security, Support letters, Veterans Administration--Education/Home, 1978-1979 (Box 588)
    - Veterans Administration, Pacific Graduate School of Psychology, 1978-1979 (Box 589)
  - Subject file (alpha file codes)
    - "A--District--American Electronic Association" to "A1--District (Santa Clara County)--San Jose State University,", 1976-1978
    - "A1--District (Santa Clara County)--Santa Clara County Bar Association" to "A3--District (Cities)--East Palo Alto--Nairobi Cultural Center/CETA,", 1977-1978 (Box 590)
    - "A3--District (Cities)--East Palo Alto--August 1977 meeting and follow-up" to "C--California--Initiatives--Rent control--Prop 13--Rent relief,", 1977-1978 (Box 591)
    - "C--California--Redwood park" to "L--Law enforcement--Office of Federal Contract Compliance,", 1976-1978 (Box 592)
  - Subject file (numeric file codes)
    - "8855--Department file/Casework--Office of Minority Business Enterprise (OMBE)" to "8905--Department file/Casework--EPA (Environmental Protection Agency,", 1976-1978
    - "8970--Department file/Casework--Federal Communications Commission" to "22500-Health--parapsychology/psychologists,", 1976-1978 (Box 593)
    - "24000--Indians" to "32000--Welfare--HEW child care,", 1977-1979 (Box 594)
  - Letters sent (pink copies). A - Z, 1979
  - Miscellany (Box 595)
    - Schedules, 1975-1978
    - Memoranda from district office and Washington staff, 1977-1978
    - Employment, resumes, interns
    - Constituent meetings
    - Opponents
    - Recommendations and referrals
    - Binding arbitration
    - Political--General
    - Pete's views, 1970-1977
  - Casework (Box 596)